(Howard's Mother:)Were you playing with him?
For God's sake, Ma, I'm 26 years old.
(Howard's Mother:)Excuse me, Mr. Grownup.
- What do you want for breakfast?
- Chocolate milk and Eggos, please.
- Howard, listen to me.
- Hang on. Call waiting.
- No, don't... Don't...
- Hello?
(Sheldon:)Howard, I'm sick.
[IMITATING MRS. WOLOWITZ]
Howard's sleeping. This is his mother.
(Howard(imitating his mother's voice):)Why are you calling
at this ungodly hour?
(Sheldon:)I need soup.
(Howard:)Then call your own mother.
[LINE BEEPS]
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
It was Sheldon.
- I tried to stop you.
- It's my own fault.
(Howard:)I forgot the protocol we put in place
after the great ear infection of '06.
(Leonard:)You call Koothrappali.
(Leonard:)We need to find a place to lay low
for the next 18 to 24 hours.